That's amazing, see.
すごいかな、ほら
Do you like being fucked?
サバサバされるの好き?
I like the gentle feel.
優しい感じが好きなんだ
I'm getting wet anyway.
どうせ濡れちゃってる
Can you see how wet it is?
濡れてるの分かる?
He's sleeping.
寝てるじゃん
Just press this a little bit more and do it before.
もうちょっとこれを押して前にやって
If you go, do it.
もし行くときは、やってね
I'm getting wet.
濡れてきちゃった
What, are you going?
え、行くの?
Now
さっ
I got wet.
き 濡れちゃった
difficult?
難しい?
It's so beautiful.
すごい綺麗だね
Are you lending money in the summer?
夏にお金を貸してる?
Do you agree with me too?
自分でも沿ってる?
I'm following it myself.
自分で沿ってるんだ
So beautiful.
すごい綺麗
Pan-pan,
パンパン、
Panpan.
パ ンパン
It's going to hurt.
痛くなっちゃう
What do you think of this?
どうですか、これは?
I wonder if I'll fall.
落ちんじゃいかな
I haven't received it yet.
受けてがない
It's true.
本当だ
You looked good, right?
上手く見たでしょ?
You're really good at it.
すごい上手じゃん
This is the constriction.
ここが、くびれが
A lot of spit comes out.
ツバいっぱい出るね
You can jerk off like this with the spit.
ツバでさ、こう、シコシコできる
You can spit on it and jerk off.
ツバつけて、シコシコできる
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
He's really good at it.
めっちゃ上手い
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Because it feels so good at the waist.
くびれのところがめっちゃ気持ちいいから
Are you not very good at it?
めっちゃ上手くない?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Oh no, no no.
やばい、やばい
It feels good.
気持ち気持ちいい
No, no, no.
ダメ、ダメ、ダメ
I'm going.
行っちゃう
You're really good at it.
め っちゃ上手いな
Uncle, I'll be leaving soon.
おじさんすぐ行っちゃうよ、これ
It feels so good.
めっちゃ気持ちいい
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいいよ
You're not used to it.
お前慣れてないね
Wave your hand behind me.
後ろに手を振ってね
Stand your feet normally.
足を普通に立てて
A small dog.
小さなわんこち
Love the back too.
後ろも気に入れよう
You're so small, pussy.
ちっちゃいね、おまんこ
Don't you want to be big too?
おじさんも大きくいたくない?
It fits in a very small place.
めっちゃ小さいところにつっぽり入ってる
terrible.
やばい
Your pussy is too small.
おまんこ小さすぎる
Don't move your legs.
足を動かすな
It feels good, it feels good.
気持ちいい、気持ちいい
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Open your uncle's hand.
おじさんの手を開く
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Stand your feet up.
足を立てる
My uncle also came out a little.
おじさんも少し出ちゃった
It came out a little.
少し出ちゃった
air
気
It lasts a long time.
持 ちいい
It came out a lot.
めっちゃ出ちゃった
Quickly, quickly, quickly.
早 く、早く、早く
It came out a lot.
めっちゃ出ちゃった
Oh no, I gave it too much.
やばい、出せすぎた
It came out a lot.
めっちゃ出ちゃった
terrible.
やばい
There were a lot of fakes out there.
偽物くらい出ちゃった
Did it feel good?
気持ちよかった?
Was it tough at the end?
最後、奥、きつかった?
There were a lot of bubbles.
めっちゃ泡ができた
Feels good.
気持ちいい
It's huge.
め っちゃでかい
That's fine.
いいじゃん
It's huge.
めっちゃでかい
That's amazing.
もうすげえ
My uncle touches me.
おじさんに触られます
My ears hurt.
耳が痛い
I'll definitely come.
めっちゃ来ますよ
I'll go.
行くよ
go, go,
行く、行く、
go.
行 く
It came out a lot.
めっちゃ出ちゃった
Can you hide?
ひっこひっこできる?
With a little finger.
少し指で
What do you think?
どうですか?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?